[whirring, clacking]
[beeping]
-[water dripping]
-[beeping continues]
[machine beeping]
[all groaning softly]
[♪ tense music playing]
[groans softly]
[bones crackle]
[crew chattering]
You gonna eat that, mate?
Yeah, I was.
Not supposed to have
a heavy meal before cryo.
-Thank you so much.
-I'm telling you that as your doctor.
-You're not a doctor.
-Yeah, well, fair enough.
-[crew member laughing]
-[chattering continues]
[Rahim] You all right there, gorgeous?
[sighing] Honestly,
cryo really creeps me out.
[Morrow] Mmm, I wonder why.
That's 'cause Teng over there
with his little beady eyes,
-stares at you while you sleep.
-[chuckles]
[Rahim] Fucking hell.
The girl should know.
[Chibuzo chuckling]
-[Chibuzo] He doesn't do that. Anymore.
-[Rahim] Of course, he does. He does.
[Morrow] Of course not.
[Chibuzo] Morrow talked to him.
Didn't you?
Mr. Teng won't be a problem unless
he wants to work 65 years for no pay.
-[Rahim scoffs]
-[all] Ooh, Teng.
Stingy.
[Petrovitch] Teng, we love you.
[Rahim] He's a nice guy.
Why you being like that?
-How did you sleep?
-Good.
-[Rahim] Wait. Sorry, say that again.
-[crew giggling]
-[Malachite] What's that one?
-[Chibuzo chuckles]
[Morrow] It's company policy.
-Say that's Weyland-Yutani--
-That's us?
Yeah, that's who we work for.
-Oh, okay.
-Right?
And they control North and South America.
-And the Moon, right?
-No, that's Dynamic.
Yutani has Mars and Saturn.
Yeah, but we're talking about the Earth.
Who rules what.
The kid hasn't done his social studies.
There's four companies.
They govern the entire globe.
Don't forget the new one. Prodigy.
[Malachite] What's that one?
Uh, it's, uh, synths, AI.
Was started by a kid maybe ten years ago?
-Yeah. Boy Kavalier.
-[chuckles]
-[Morrow] That's the one.
-[Petrovitch] Youngest trillionaire ever.
[Shmuel]
Right. So, there's five companies, right?
-[Malachite] I still don't get it.
-[Zaveri chuckles] Poor baby.
[Morrow] Mr. Teng.
You checked the nav computer, Mr. Teng?
Are you asking if I did my job?
How long to Earth's orbit?
10,525,000 seconds.
Plenty of… time.
Months, Teng. Give it to me in months.
-[Teng] Four months.
-[chuckling] Such a jerk.
Give or take a few days.
You all good, Captain?
Hey.
Comms are down.
Looks like the log files are corrupted.
Well, it's probably just a glitch.
I can have a look.
No. Security will investigate.
We're also burning way too much fuel.
I want you and Teng looking into
what system we could shut down.
[Shmuel] Why don't we just,
uh, shoot Chibuzo's specimens into space
and shut down her little zoo?
Okay. I think he means real suggestions.
[Shmuel] This is a real suggestion.
Those things give me the creeps.
-[Malachite] Yeah, me too.
-The specimens are the mission.
Easy for you to say, cyborg.
We lost a lot of good men getting them.
And for what?
So the company can put shit into
our breakfast cereal to control our minds?
-Okay. That is not a real thing.
-[Dinsdale chuckles] No.
[Rahim] Don't know
what you're talking about, mate.
The specimens are the mission. Period.
Do I need to post extra security,
or restrict you to your quarters?
[inhales]
[♪ eerie music playing]
[exhales sharply]
Sullivan, Petrovitch.
Got it.
Wake me on final approach.
[Zaveri] Will do.
[Rahim] See you later, mate.
[Chibuzo] Did he say minefield?
[Rahim] I prefer to go back to bed,
do you know what I mean?
[♪ jazz playing over speakers]
[♪ performer sings in French]
[performer] Thank you very much.
And hello.
[metal clinks]
[♪ jazz music continues]
[creatures chittering]
-[Malachite] You got any bedtime stories?
-[Shmuel speaks indistinctly]
-[cat meowing]
-[Malachite chuckles]
[creatures chittering]
[creaking]
[breathes sharply]
[♪ jazz music continues, fades]
[distorted shout]
[♪ tense music playing]
[distorted screams]
[screeching]
[birds chirping]
What is it?
It's a scorpion.
Where did it come from?
It was in the mess.
What are you gonna do with it?
What do you think we should do with it?
Squash it,
so it doesn't sting you.
What if, while I'm squashing it, another
scorpion stings me to protect its friend
the same way you're trying to protect me?
It scares me.
Think of how the scorpion must feel.
Trapped under glass,
menaced by giants.
Okay, my darling.
It's time.
Do we have to?
Yes.
Go on. I'll be here when you wake up.
Are you gonna kill it?
Do you want me to?
No.
Is it gonna hurt?
Told you, it's just like… falling asleep.
Will I dream?
I don't know. You'll have to tell me
when you wake up.
[door alarm beeps]
Ah, there she is.
Hi.
Uh, you got a little something, uh… Boop.
[both chuckle]
[Arthur] All right.
Deep breath for me.
[Marcy breathes deeply]
[Arthur] There you go.
[Arthur] You know, I had
the weirdest dream last night.
We had a baby and it was a pig.
[Dame Sylvia] Oh, wow.
I had a pig when I was a girl.
It was cute. Then it was 300 pounds.
[Arthur] Huh. So more of a human child
is what we want then.
[Dame Sylvia] We talked about this.
These are our children.
[Dame Sylvia] Now focus.
Is that what I'm gonna look like?
Yes. That's you.
-She's pretty.
-[Dame Sylvia chuckles]
-[machine beeps]
-[door opens]
Okay. Willkommen.
Moshi moshi. [chuckles]
How's our girl?
-She's ready.
-[Boy Kavalier grunts]
Do you know who Neil Armstrong was?
He was an astronaut.
Not just an astronaut.
He was the first man
to set foot on the Moon.
You're gonna be the first too.
I'm going to the Moon?
[chuckles] No… [chuckles] …silly.
You're gonna be the first person
to transition from a human body
to a synthetic.
Because I'm special.
[Boy Kavalier] That's right.
You're very, very… [chuckles] …special.
Do you want to see a magic trick? Yeah?
[imitates wind whistling]
[chuckles]
[Boy Kavalier] It's pretty cool. Right?
Okay, you. Up on the table.
I want my brother.
I told you, you can see him…
when you wake up.
But he can't see me.
[smacks lips] No.
Because it's a secret. What we're doing.
Yes.
Come on.
Is it time to go to sleep?
That's right, Marcy.
Wendy.
What was that?
She looks like a Wendy.
[machinery revs]
[machine whirring]
[whirring continues]
[child singing]
♪ Latch on to the affirmative ♪
-♪ And don't mess with Mr. In-Between ♪
-[baby babbling]
[seagulls squawking]
[♪ "Killer Crane" playing]
♪ After the rain ♪
♪ A killer crane ♪
♪ After the rainbow ♪
[seagulls squawking]
♪ Across the sky, her graces glide ♪
♪ Across the sea ♪
♪ Across crea… ♪
[Dame Sylvia shouting] Wendy.
Wendy!
We're ready for you!
♪ Sunshine
I saw you through the hanging vine ♪
♪ Fading away ♪
Race you.
♪And the sound
Steals the ground unafraid ♪
-[♪ ominous music playing]
-[birds chirping]
[Dame Sylvia] Wendy, darling…
how are you feeling today?
These are weird.
Your breasts?
They're weird.
They move around when I run.
Well, you are in an adult body now.
[chuckles]
Why?
Because synthetic bodies don't grow.
So?
How are your emotions?
You been happy? Sad?
I don't know.
[whispers] They're quiet now.
The human body manufactures hormones,
dopamine, serotonin, estrogen,
that create moods.
You don't have those anymore.
We've tried to simulate them.
To simulate adolescence,
as you grow into your adult body,
so it's not just like flipping a switch.
But maybe
we need to increase the intensity.
We've had this discussion.
She's not human anymore.
Why are we pretending she is?
"She" is sitting right there,
and it's the protocol
as laid out by the CEO.
The body is a vessel for the mind.
A human mind, on its path to endless life.
Simulating the human experience
is critical.
So, what am I?
If I'm not human,
what am I?
Whatever you want to be.
[Dame Sylvia] I got you something,
for your collection.
Oh, and I have good news.
The other children have arrived.
I'm not alone anymore?
Darling, you're never alone. You got us.
But yes, now, there will be others.
Like me?
Not yet.
They're still children.
So we need to help them to make
the transition, so they're not afraid.
Can you do that?
Can you be a big sister?
[Wendy] Listen now. Hear up!
You can grow big and strong like me.
Who wants a ride?
[all] Me! Me! Me! Me! Me! Me!
-[Wendy laughs]
-[chuckles]
-Whoa.
-[children laughing]
[Wendy] And you'll be super fast too.
Were you sick too? Before.
Dying even. And everybody was so sad.
But then the boy genius came along,
and he said… [finger snaps]
"Don't be sad.
I'm gonna fix you right up."
And that's exactly what he did.
He gave me this big girl body.
Better than new.
Now I'm the forever girl.
[Child Slightly]
Because grown-up minds don't fit?
Uh, because grown-up minds are too stiff,
so they can't make the trip yet,
but our minds, kid minds,
we fit just right.
Question?
Will I be able to walk again?
You'll be able to walk,
run, jump, dance. [chuckles]
-[Wendy] Do you guys like to dance?
-[all] Yeah.
-Question?
-I want to be a scientist when I grow up.
Okay. That's not a question,
but cool.
[Wendy chuckles]
When do we get to go home?
You don't.
[chuckles]
I'll be here the whole time, okay?
Promise?
Promise.
Uh, can you move, please? I need to begin.
Go around.
You want to see a magic trick?
Yeah.
[machine whirring]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[whirring continues]
[Boy Kavalier] "Mrs. Darling
first heard of Peter
when she was tidying up
her children's minds.
It is the nightly custom
of every good mother,
after her children are asleep,
to rummage in their minds
and put things straight.
When you wake in the morning,
the naughtinesses and evil passions
with which you went to bed,
have been folded up small
and placed at the bottom of your mind.
And on the top, beautifully aired,
are spread out your prettier thoughts,
ready for you to put on.
In the old days,
at home,
the Neverland had always begun to look
a little dark and threatening by bedtime.
Then unexplored patches arose in it
and spread.
Black shadows moved about in them.
The roar of the beasts of prey
was quite different now, and above all,
you lost the certainty
that you would win."
[♪ dramatic music continues]
[alarm blaring]
-[clattering]
-[cat growling]
[Mother] Collision imminent.
-[distorted screaming]
-[Mother] Collision imminent.
[beeping]
[beeping continues]
[alarm blaring]
-[alarm stops]
-[beeping]
Morrow!
[muffled] Morrow! Let me in!
Please! It's coming.
-[alarm blaring]
-Let me in!
[alarm stops]
[muffled] Morrow, let me in!
-[alarm blaring]
-What are you doing? Let me in!
[muffled] It's coming.
Hurry. Hurry up. It's coming.
No. What are you doing?
No, no, no. Let me in!
Morrow! Oh, no!
Why are you doing this?
You fucking asshole!
[Morrow humming]
-[humming continues]
-[Zaveri crying] No.
[Zaveri] No!
[grunting]
-[creature screeching]
-[Zaveri screaming]
-[Morrow humming]
-[thudding]
-[creature chattering]
-[Zaveri groaning]
[hisses, growls]
[screeches]
[screeching]
[metal rattling]
Mother, I need the impact room.
[screeching]
[Mother] Collision imminent.
-[screeching]
-[Mother] Collision imminent.
-[Morrow humming]
-[banging]
-[Mother] Collision imminent.
-[squealing]
-[humming continues]
-[machine whirring]
[Mother] Collision imminent.
-[squealing continues]
-[Mother] Impact in T-minus ten seconds.
[Mother] Nine…
[Mother] …four, three, two…
[alarm blares]
[train horn blaring]
[motorcycle revving]
[commentator 1 speaking indistinctly]
[commentator 2] Yeah,
like you were saying.
Easy pop-up to center field.
That's two down.
[♪ rap music playing]
[exhales sharply]
[Wendy] Well, I'm glad you asked.
See ya.
[Wendy] His name is Joe.
Joe DiMaggio, like the baseball player.
[commentator 2] Counts two and two
and we're in third. Ready to break.
[baseball bat cracks]
[commentator 2]
Oh, Wilson got a hold of it.
It's got the height,
and it's got the distance.
Two-run homer for Wilson.
-[Joe] Yes!
-And… take the lead. Two to nothing.
[Wendy] What does he do?
Well, he's a medic.
Like a doctor.
Hello.
Dad used to always say that.
Where are you going?
Medic's pretty cool.
[chuckles]
He's really good at it too.
She…
She's watching the brother again.
[Wendy] Who does he work for?
He works for Prodigy.
Just like us.
He has to work with soldiers,
who work with guns.
They told him I died.
[chattering]
[both speaking Thai]
[Wendy] What's for dinner?
I miss eating.
[baseball commentary continues]
[exhales sharply] There you are.
[Diego] Am I hallucinating,
or is that ice coming straight towards us?
[Manny] Yeah, yeah, it's coming.
It sounds like there's animals on it.
[Sid] Yippee! We're being rescued!
We're being rescued!
[Diego] I hear laughter.
[Sid] Must be a party cruise.
[Captain Gutt] Ahoy, down there!
You know, these waters
are infested with pirates.
-Captain Gutt here to help!
-[chuckles]
[Manny] Look, we don't want any trouble.
-Now surrender your ship or face my…
-Surrender your ship or face my…
-…fury.
-Or face your furry what?
-[Captain Gutt] Not "furry." Fury!
-Fury. [chuckles]
[Captain Gutt] Fire!
Good night, Joe.
Let's go.
[Rashidi] Now? Really? [sighs]
Hey, uh, what did the robot say yesterday?
I gotta serve out my contract.
Right.
-[grunts]
-Come on.
[Rashidi] Hey, eyes on the ball, Brahma.
[metal rattling]
What about medical school?
So we're stuck with you.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
-You love me.
-Babe.
-[exhales sharply]
-You're just afraid to say the words.
[Rashidi] Holy shit!
-[Siberian] What the fuck?
-Call it in.
-Captain…
-Call it in!
-[clamoring]
-Everyone okay?
[Siberian] This is Sigma-Prime. We have
a downed spacecraft, multiple casualties.
We're heading to the crash site.
[horn honking]
[indistinct radio chatter]
All right, by the book.
Locate the survivors,
evacuate the wounded, secure the site.
[all] Yes, sir!
[siren wailing]
[tires screeching]
-[air brakes hissing]
-[siren blaring]
-[Nagg] Members, check your weapons.
-[all] Yes, sir.
Check.
[Nagg] Brahma, upstairs.
Prep to evac the wounded.
[Brahma] Yes, sir.
-Rashidi, take four to the ground floor.
-Yes, sir.
[Nagg] We're moving!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go! Move, move, move!
Let's search for the wounded now!
-[people clamoring]
-[Nagg] Two by two!
Come on then! Come on then!
[echoing] Come on now!
-[distorted echoes]
-[siren wailing]
[Nagg] There we go!
Bring it down! Bring it down!
-[civilian 1] Help! Help! Help!
-[people clamoring]
[metal creaking]
[Rashidi] Keep moving, keep moving!
Hermit, with me, with me, let's go!
-Medic tent to the right!
-Keep going!
If you're hurt, head to the medics!
There's more medics coming!
-[Rashidi] Keep moving!
-[clamoring continues]
-[officer 1] Go! Go! Go!
-[officer 2] Get inside!
[siren wailing]
[Nagg] Move! Move! Move! Go! Go! Go!
Let's move it, people!
-Two that way, three that way.
-Yes, sir.
Follow me.
[announcer through PA system]
[Hermit] Anybody injured?
[Rashidi] Security services!
-[Hermit] Anybody hurt?
-[Rashidi] Search and rescue!
[Siberian] Search and rescue!
[Rashidi] Search and rescue! Moving in!
[Hermit] Search and rescue!
-[Hermit] Search and rescue!
-[Rashidi] Hermit!
-[Hermit] Got it.
-[Rashidi] Yeah.
[Siberian] Search and rescue!
[Rashidi] Search and rescue!
Keep up.
[announcer through PA system continues]
[Rashidi] Ears on.
I've got voices down here.
[Rashidi] Security services!
-You good?
-[Siberian] Yes.
[Rashidi] Search and rescue.
[Siberian] Search and rescue!
-[Hermit] Anybody hurt?
-[Siberian] Search and rescue!
-[baby crying]
-[person shrieks]
[barking]
Control the dog, man.
-[Hermit] Search and rescue!
-[Rashidi] Coming in!
-[Siberian] Cap.
[Rashidi] Hermit! You all right?
-Please evacuate the building.
-Coming in.
-Use the medical center outside.
-Hermit!
-[Hermit] Sir, can you hear me?
-[Siberian] We got medical.
-Hey, Anant, give some blood to Hermit.
-[Anant] Got it.
-You all right, Hermit?
-Yes.
-[Siberian] Search and rescue!
-[Rashidi] Search and rescue!
-[Cortez] Is he gone?
-[Rashidi] Hermit?
[Hermit] Holy shit.
[electricity crackling]
[Rashidi] Looks like she goes
all the way down.
-[Rashidi] Cortez.
-Yes, sir.
-Radio for a fire suppression unit.
-[Cortez] Got it, Cap.
[Rashidi] Anybody smells sulfur,
call it out.
-[Rashidi] Let's move in.
-[Siberian] Roger.
-This is Cortez to dispatch.
-[radio chattering]
We have a 10-50 F situation.
I repeat, we have a 10-50 F situation.
[indistinct radio chatter]
[♪ tense music playing]
[Cortez] We got multiple injuries,
a death, and property damage.
Requesting for an ambulance…
[Siberian] Search and rescue!
Good luck, guys.
Fucking hell.
Come on.
Look at the size of that thing.
-I should have called in sick.
-[chuckles]
Well, don't worry,
I brought spare panties in my pack.
[chuckles]
[Hoyt coughs]
Come on.
What kind of ship is this?
Science vessel, I think.
It's Weyland-Yutani.
I used to collect the cards
when I was a kid.
Think there's a finder's fee?
Lock that shit down.
[hissing]
Hoyt, Anant.
-Copy that.
-Let's move.
Let's move. With me.
[electrical humming]
[electricity crackling]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[breathing heavily]
-[TV continues, indistinct]
-[electricity crackling]
[hissing]
Mother, this is Morrow. Alert Weyland HQ.
The ship has been boarded.
Status of cargo unknown.
I'm moving to the armory and will secure
the site until reinforcements can arrive.
[Wendy humming]
All right.
I need you to put these on.
And when you hear a tone, raise your hand.
-Okay. [chuckles]
Why don't you have kids?
Well, we t… we tried to have kids,
but I… I have a low sperm count.
-Sperm. [chuckles]
-Yeah, sperm. It's a funny word.
Isn't a sperm what comes out of a boy
and then goes into the girl's egg?
Yes, that's right.
Yeah.
[technician 1] She's beyond
all human frequencies, 75,000 Hz.
Oh, Wendy, we're, uh…
Put these back on,
we're not… we're finished yet.
-[technician 1] What's she--
-[Arthur] Shh!
[people screaming and clamoring]
[breathes shakily]
[Atom Eins] The ship touched down
at 17:30.
It's a deep space
research vessel, C class.
Weyland-Yutani.
Survivors?
On the ship? Unknown. Comms are down.
The ship must have clipped the tower.
But we have forces on the ground.
Mass casualties, I'd imagine,
among the residents.
Luckily, it was
the Founder's Day festival.
-Hundreds of people were at the park.
-[Boy Kavalier] Mmm.
-Sir--
-Not now.
-Let's go.
-Uh, no. No.
[Boy Kavalier] Triage the rescue
by income bracket. Call up the reserves,
and keep this quiet
until we know the damage.
We can do it.
And the ship?
Ooh, uh, a deep space research vessel
loaded with who knows what?
I think that's ours now.
She won't like that.
-Yutani.
-Yeah, so she can sue.
I said we can do it.
Sir, we're fast, we're strong,
we don't break.
You made us. We can do it.
Rescue people, clean up.
Why?
The brother from her old life,
he's a medic with the tactical unit.
They're inside the tower.
[Boy Kavalier] So you want to help him?
Look at her face.
Her body language.
I mean, if I didn't know better,
I'd say she was human.
I am human.
[chuckles]
Send them.
-Send…
-[Boy Kavalier] Yeah, the Lost Boys.
Let's see how they handle the stress.
I want all technicians on deck.
Monitor brain function,
emotional response,
see how the enhanced physiognomy performs.
Sir, they're not first responders.
They're still in the prototype stage,
the loss of a single unit
will be devastating.
Yeah, yeah. So don't lose one.
You'll watch them?
And they can follow orders, I mean…
You can follow orders, right?
Sir, yes, sir.
See?
Off you pop.
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[chuckles]
I was sick before we got sick.
Like, always sick, kind of.
"No immune system," my mum said.
Not me.
Healthy as a horse. [imitates gunfire]
Why a horse? Are they extremely healthy?
Hmm. Anything is only ever as healthy
as it is, 100% being the healthiest.
I didn't like it.
Being sick.
-[scoffs] Nobody likes it.
-[Nibs laughs]
No.
It was scary.
Lying in my bed every night
thinking I could die.
[Slightly] Now we can't die.
We can still be crushed or, like,
explode though.
Or be set on fire. Wait, could we drown?
Yeah, like a hippo could come
and maul us or a crocodile--
But not grow old or get cancer.
Right?
Maybe our batteries
just run out and we're, like…
[imitates machine powering down]
-[blows raspberry]
-[all laughing]
[Wendy] Standing, dressing, running.
We got a life-or-death
spaceship crash rescue mission.
Seriously?
[♪ tense music playing]
[electricity crackling]
[electronic screeching]
[crackling continues]
[Hoyt] Search and rescue! Is anyone here?
[electronic screeching]
You first.
[sighs]
Of course.
Oh, fuck!
[Hoyt] Oh, man.
What the hell is that?
[gasps, exhales sharply]
[chuckles]
Come check this out.
You think he died in the crash?
[Anant] He's been shot.
Two to the body, one in the head.
-[thuds]
-[creature chittering]
[Anant breathing heavily]
[Hoyt] Let's get the fuck out of here.
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
[metal clangs]
[Morrow] Don't turn around.
Slowly, weapons on the ground.
Relax, friend,
we're Prodigy search and rescue.
You've been in a crash.
Just let me call the med team.
-[gunshot]
-[Hoyt] Fuck. [breathing heavily]
Don't make me say it again.
[metal clinking]
Side arms.
Up.
Back in the lab.
Move.
-[Anant breathing heavily]
-[Morrow] Stop.
On the floor, back to the pipe.
Dude, this building is gonna come down
any second.
Cuff him to the pipe.
[zip tie zipping]
Now you.
-[zip tie zipping]
-[grunts]
-[metal clanks]
-Seriously. We won't even call it in.
Just let us go and we'll pretend
this never happened, all right?
[metal clanks]
Where is Kavalier?
The trillionaire?
How the fuck would I know?
[Anant softly] Oh, shit.
Hey, he's a cyborg.
Mother, lab specimens seem intact.
Moving to track the fugitives.
Brother, come on.
You can't leave us like this.
I'm not your brother.
[♪ ominous music playing]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[Siberian] Hey.
-[static on radio]
-[Rashidi] Command, are you seeing this?
We're inside the cryo-chamber.
Looks like no survivors.
[distorted radio chatter]
[Rashidi] Command?
-[Siberian] Hermit!
-[Hermit] I'm coming.
[Siberian] What does that?
[Hermit] I don't know.
He's been dead a week, maybe more.
You see the color of the blood?
-[Siberian] Yeah.
-The coagulation.
[Siberian] Wait, why did this ship crash?
Hermit.
[Rashidi] Something crawled out of here.
[Siberian] What does that mean?
[electricity crackles]
[Hermit]
We gotta find what made that trail.
[♪ eerie music playing]
[Anant] Hey! We're in here!
I think I can get my knife.
Almost got it. [grunts, whimpers]
-Jesus.
-[Anant] What?
Something's on me.
[Anant] What do you mean
something's on you?
-I don't know. Fuck me.
-[Anant] Hoyt?
Some kind of big-ass bug.
-[Anant] What?
-[creature chitters]
-[Hoyt grunting]
-[Anant] Fuck. Huh?
-[groaning, breathing heavily]
-[Anant] Fuck. Fuck.
Hoyt, come on, we need to stand up.
I can't get it off!
-Hoyt! We need to get up!
-Fuck!
-Where's it gone? I can't see it.
-[Anant] Huh?
[Hoyt screams]
Hoyt!
It fucking bit me!
-Hoyt, stand up!
-[shrieking] Fuck!
[groans]
-Fuck! Hoyt!
-[groans]
-[Hoyt breathing heavily]
-Hoyt.
Hoyt.
Hoyt!
Fuck! [grunting, breathing heavily]
[whimpers]
[grunting]
Oh, no. [grunting]
No. No. Fuck. Fuck. No. [grunts]
[screams]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[Slightly groans]
[machine whirring]
Used to be food, you know.
[scoffs] Me?
Humanity.
Your lives were short
and filled with fear.
Then your brains grew.
You built tools and used them
to conquer nature.
You built impossible machines
and went to space.
You stopped being food.
Or, I should say,
you told yourself
you weren't food anymore.
But, in the animal kingdom,
there is always someone bigger or smaller,
who would eat you alive
if they had the chance.
That's what it is to be an animal.
You're born, you live, you die.
[metal rattling]
-[explosion]
-[groaning]
My brother is not gonna die.
Of course he will.
[Siberian yelps]
[Rashidi] Everyone okay?
[Siberian] Yeah.
Boss?
We keep going.
[Kirsh] Injury, illness, old age.
They all do.
Generation after generation.
All we can do is watch and take names.
No.
[♪ "E5150" playing]
He's not gonna die.
I'm gonna save him.
[♪ "The Mob Rules" playing]